Guide to the Louis H. Roddis Papers, 1823-1990 RL.01102
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Miscellaneous
  - SE2 Status Update: Pane v. NRC, 1982, June (Box 103)
  - Remarks by NRC before New York Society of Security Analysts, 1983, Jan. 19 (Box 103)
  - Under Secretary of Defense Letter on Political Advocacy, 1983, Jan. 20 (Box 103)
  - Nuclear Developments in Europe, 1983 May 31 (Box 103)
  - Report on Regulatory Activities, 1983 (Box 103)
  - American Nuclear Energy Council Materials, 1984, Apr. 4 (Box 103)
  - The National Academics Report to Senior Government Officials, 1985 (Box 103)
  - LHR Report on Standard Nuclear Plant Design, 1985, Jan. 19 (Box 103)
  - Report on Backfitting and Licensing Practices at the U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 1985, Mar. 11 (Box 103)
  - Sandia Report: Peer Review Comments on Draft NUREG/Cr-1278 Final Report, 1985, May (Box 103)
  - Construction Prudency Investigation, 1985, Nov. 20 (Box 103)
  - H.O. Reinsch Presentation for Nuclear Energy Forum, 1986, Jan. 29 (Box 103)
  - Leadership in Achieving Operational Excellence--A Report to the U.S. Nuclear Utility Industry, 1986, Aug. (Box 103)
  - Louis H. Roddis, Jr.--Report to Secretary of Energy Herrington, 1986, Oct. 3 (Box 103)
  - National Association of Regulatory Utility commissioners, Report of the Ad-Hoc Committee on Insurance, 1987, Mar. 4 (Box 103)
  - Sponsor Resolution Opposing NRC Emergency Planning Rule Change, 1987, Mar. 9 (Box 103)
  - Worldwatch Paper 81: Renewable Energy: Today's Contribution, Tomorrow's promise, 1988, Jan. (Box 103)
  - Overseas Advisory Associates, Inc.: Summary of Japan's Fast Reactor Program, 1989, Nov. (Box 103)
  - General Motors Public Interest Report, 1990 (Box 103)
  - Power Generation of the Top 100 Electric Companies, 1973, July (Box 104)
  - Central Station Nuclear Plans, 1974, Feb. 25 (Box 104)
  - Rhode Island Public Utilities Commission Investigation of Economics of Nuclear Power (Box 104)
  - 1981 Performance Award Presentation for the Vermont Yankee Nuclear Plan, 1982, Apr. 1 (Box 104)
  - Materials on Pacific Gas and Electric company Diablo Canyon Power Plant Unit 2, 1985, Nov., 2 folders (Box 104)
  - The North Carolina Alternative Energy Corporation:
    - Annual Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 104)
    - Quarterly Status Reports, 1985, Oct.-1988, Mar., 5 folders (Box 104)
  - Virginia Power/ North Carolina Power/ West Virginia Power: Virginia Natural Gas: Quality, Productivity, Innovation:
    - The Seven Fundamentals, 1985, Nov. (Box 104)
    - Through Employee Involvement Teams, 1985, Jan. (Box 104)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company:
    - North Anna Unit 1 Steam Generator Tube Rupture Event Report, 1987, Aug. 17 (Box 104)
    - North Anna Unit 1 Steam Generator Rub Rupture Event and Presentation, 1987, Aug. 28, Sept. 15, 2 folders (Box 104)
  - Northwest Power Planning Council Annual Report, 1987-1990, 4 folders (Box 104)
  - Utah Power and Light Company Before the Federal Energy Regulatory Commission, undated (Box 104)
  - Oglethorpe Electric Membership Corporation (OEMC): Correspondence:
    - 1976, Dec. 23 (Box 104)
    - 1979, Apr.-Aug. (Box 104)
  - Nuclear Plan Reliability Data System Program Description, 1986, Feb. (Box 104)
  - Electricity from Nuclear Power: Booklet Order form, 1987 (Box 104)
  - A Plan for the Development of Magnetic Fusion Energy, 1990, Mar. (Box 104)
  - Materials from the International Conference on Large High Voltage Electric Systems, 1978, Aug. 30-Sept. 7 (Box 105)
  - Workshop on Public Policy High Capacity Aspects of Electric Power Transmission, 1979, May 14-16 (Box 105)
  - The Foresight Group, 1980, Apr. 17 (Box 105)
  - International Conference on Enhanced Safety of Nuclear Reactors, 1988, Aug. 8-10 (Box 105)
  - Panero-Tizian Associates: Correspondence, 1976 (Box 105)
  - Turbodyne materials, 1975-1977 (Box 105)
  - Turbodyne Corporation:
    - Correspondence and brochure, 1977 (Box 105)
    - Materials, 1977 (Box 105)
  - The BDM Corporation: Information Portfolio, 1982 (Box 105)
  - Overview of Access Charges, 1985, Apr. (Box 105)
  - Overview of Bypass, 1985, Apr. (Box 105)
  - Albright Triple Hybrid Automobile, undated (Box 105)
  - Employee Manual on Voter Registration, undated (Box 105)
  - Science and Engineering Indicators, 1987 (Box 105)
  - Minutes of the Twenty-Fourth National Academy of Engineering: Annual Meeting, 1988, Sept. 29 (Box 105)
  - National Academy of Engineering Program Report: Fiscal Year 1988 (Box 105)
  - National Academy of Engineering's Outstanding Achievements, 1964-1989 (Box 105)
  - University of Virginia: Energy Policy Studies Center booklet, 1982, Feb. (Box 105)
  - National Science Foundation: Guide to Programs, 1991 (Box 105)
  - Utility Sales Sheet, undated (Box 105)
  - Financial Analysis of a Group of Petroleum Companies, undated (Box 105)
  - Questech, Inc.: 3rd Quarter Report, 1988 (Box 105)
  - Drug Science Foundation: Correspondence, 1982, Feb. 1 (Box 105)
  - Inactive Nuclear Book Draft, 1958 (Box 105)
  - Mark's Handbook 7th, 8th, 9th Editions, 1972-1988, 6 folders (Box 105)
  - Book Review on Raymond L. Murray's Nuclear Energy, 1988 (Box 105)
  - IEEE's Corona and Field Effects of AC Overhead Transmission Lines: Information for Decision Makers, 1985, July (Box 105)
  - Superconducting Power Transmission Test Results, 1985, July 14-19 (Box 105)
  - Aspen Institute's Electric Utilities: Structure and Regulation, 1986 (Box 105)
  - Advanced Engineering Plastics, Inc.: News Release, 1986, May 27 (Box 105)
  - Ship Propulsion Reactors (Encyclopedia article), undated (Box 106)
  - Society of Naval Architects and Marine Engineers and Clearance of Technical Papers on U.S.S. Nautilus, 1954 (Box 106)
  - Submarine Data, undated (Box 106)
  - Lord Abbott Co, 1977 (Box 106)
  - CoPEP (Committee on Public Engineering Policy), undated (Box 106)
  - Booklet on Coal Ash, undated (Box 106)
  - Westinghouse AP600, 1988, May (Box 106)
  - Pamphlets, 1985 (Box 106)
  - Electric Utility Information, undated (Box 106)
  - Technology Futures, Inc.: Technology Assessment of Alternate Means of Meeting Anticipated U.S. Electric Power Demands, 1982, May 3 (Box 106)
  - What Works: Documenting Energy Conservation in Buildings, 1984 (Box 106)
  - Commercial Business Dailey: Article, 1977, Oct. 5 (Box 106)
  - Correspondence, 1980, Feb. 6 (Box 106)
  - Information on The Fire Unleashed 1985, June (Box 106)
  - Naval Engineers Journal: Article, 1989, Mar. (Box 106)
- Oversize Materials
  - Energy Policy
    - 4-177, Electrical Power Discussion, by Louis H. Roddis for use in the industry, 1971 Oct. 8 (film reel) (Box 107)